=Bossy Husband Who Loved Me= =Episode 20=
= الزوج المتسلط الذي أحبني = = الحلقة 20 =
That's a good shot.
هذه لقطة جيدة.
The Sheng must be proud
يجب أن يكون Sheng فخوراً
to have Your Highness as its heir.
أن يكون سموك وريثها.
Miss Liu.
ملكة جمال ليو.
Do you want me
هل تريدني
to teach you?
ليعلمك؟
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Zhao Tie is as good an archer as I am.
تشاو تاي هو رامي جيد مثلي.
Does Miss Liu not want to learn archery anymore?
ألا تريد الآنسة ليو تعلم الرماية بعد الآن؟
I know I have no talent in this.
أعلم أنه ليس لدي موهبة في هذا.
Perhaps
ربما
I shouldn't trouble you further.
لا يجب أن أزعجك أكثر.
I envy Her Highness
أنا أحسد صاحبة السمو
for having a man like Your Highness
لوجود رجل مثل صاحب السمو
caring for her
العناية بها
and protecting her from all harm.
وحمايتها من كل مكروه.
That's why you get to live such a happy life.
لهذا السبب يمكنك أن تعيش مثل هذه الحياة السعيدة.
I'm unlike Her Highness.
أنا على عكس صاحبة السمو.
But
ولكن
I feel sorry for Your Highness.
أشعر بالأسف على صاحب السمو.
We're a couple,
نحن زوجان ،
so we should always support each other.
لذلك يجب علينا دائمًا دعم بعضنا البعض.
You saw me teaching her archery
رأيتني أعلمها الرماية
and caring for her right now.
والعناية بها الآن.
But what you didn't see was how she stood up for me
لكن ما لم تراه هو كيف دافعت عني
when we were at the royal court.
عندما كنا في الديوان الملكي.
She put her life at stake, trying to protect me.
لقد عرضت حياتها للخطر ، في محاولة لحمايتي.
I think
أظن
I owe her
أنا مدين لها
a lot.
كثيراً.
By the way,
على فكرة،
I forgot to ask you something.
لقد نسيت أن أسألك شيئا.
How old is Miss Liu?
كم عمر الآنسة ليو؟
I'm 22 years old this year.
عمري 22 سنة هذا العام.
22 years old?
22 سنة؟
Then,
ثم،
you're two years older than Princess Consort.
كنت أكبر بعامين من الأميرة القرين.
You were being too humble
كنت متواضعا جدا
when you addressed her as Elder Sister.
عندما خاطبتها باعتبارك الأخت الكبرى.
How dare he?
كيف اهتمامه؟
I have a pretty face
لدي وجه جميل
and I was offering myself to him.
وكنت أعرض عليه نفسي.
How could Qin Chuan stay unmoved?
كيف يمكن أن يظل تشين تشوان غير متأثر؟
He is...
هو...
He's toxic.
إنه سام.
He has rendered me speechless.
لقد جعلني عاجزًا عن الكلام.
He never follows the storyline.
لم يتابع القصة قط.
The beautiful girl was standing right before you.
كانت الفتاة الجميلة تقف أمامك مباشرة.
Why did you stick to me instead?
لماذا تمسكت بي بدلا من ذلك؟
However,
لكن،
Mu Xiaoxi did everything just like how I planned it.
فعل Mu Xiaoxi كل شيء تمامًا كما خططت له.
She even followed my plans several times.
حتى أنها اتبعت خططي عدة مرات.
I almost thought
كدت أفكر
she was helping me out voluntarily.
كانت تساعدني طواعية.
Besides, I can't count on
علاوة على ذلك ، لا يمكنني الاعتماد عليها
the princess of Beiqing either.
أما أميرة Beiqing.
She's supposed to be a very cunning witch.
من المفترض أن تكون ساحرة ماكرة للغاية.
I created so many opportunities for you,
لقد أوجدت لك العديد من الفرص ،
yet you grabbed none of them.
لكنك لم تمسك أيا منها.
- I need to figure out something else. - I need to find another way.
- أحتاج إلى اكتشاف شيء آخر.  - أنا بحاجة إلى إيجاد طريقة أخرى.
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
I've investigated it.
لقد حققت في الأمر.
Liu Ruyu
ليو رويو
is the princess of Beiqing,
هي أميرة Beiqing ،
Shangguan Ruyu.
شانغقوان رويو.
I didn't find her name, Shangguan Ruyu,
لم أجد اسمها ، Shangguan Ruyu ،
on the list of envoys who are visiting the Capital.
على قائمة المبعوثين الذين يزورون العاصمة.
She managed to sneak into the Capital so easily.
تمكنت من التسلل إلى العاصمة بسهولة.
That means
هذا يعني
there is a spy in the Capital.
هناك جاسوس في العاصمة.
Keep an eye on her.
راقبها.
Yes.
نعم.
Shangguan Ruyu won't be able to harm us
لن يتمكن Shangguan Ruyu من إلحاق الضرر بنا
since she's on her own.
بما أنها وحدها.
But I have another worry now.
لكن لدي قلق آخر الآن.
It seems like the princess of Beiqing
يبدو أنها أميرة Beiqing
is being manipulated by "Yuan Ju Qing" too.
يتم التلاعب به من قبل "اليوان جو تشينغ" أيضًا.
I didn't expect
لم أتوقع
this man
هذا الرجل
to be this omnipotent.
أن تكون هذا القادر.
Anyway,
على أي حال،
Xi and I
شي وأنا
will not get manipulated by him.
لن يتلاعب به.
I'm sure Her Highness will be moved beyond words
أنا متأكد من أن صاحبة السمو ستتخطى الكلمات
when she sees Your Highness doing your best to protect her.
عندما ترى سموك تبذل قصارى جهدك لحمايتها.
I read her mind.
قرأت رأيها.
She thought I was "toxic".
ظنت أنني "سامة".
She also said that she admired me,
قالت أيضًا إنها معجبة بي ،
and called me the "Sixth Brother".
ودعوني "الأخ السادس".
However,
لكن،
no matter how you see it,
لا يهم كيف تراه ،
I'm still
انا مازلت
the fourth brother, right?
الأخ الرابع صحيح؟
Yes.
نعم.
Could it be
هل من الممكن ذلك
the dialect of Her Highness' hometown?
بلهجة مسقط رأس سمو؟
Could it be "Lao Liu"?
هل يمكن أن يكون "لاو ليو"؟
"Lao Liu"?
"لاو ليو"؟
I guess...
اعتقد...
She's probably complimenting Your Highness
من المحتمل أنها تمدح سموك
for your loyalty.
من أجل ولائك.
If that's the case,
إذا كان هذا هو الحال،
you are
أنت
my "Sixth Brother" too.
"أخي السادس" أيضًا.
Oh, no.
أوه لا.
I'm flattered.
أنا أشعر بالإطراء.
You're my "Sixth Brother".
أنت "أخي السادس".
Here.
هنا.
Here's an osmanthus cake for you.
هذه كعكة أوسمانثوس لك.
Thank you, "Sixth Brother".
شكرا لك "الأخ السادس".
"Sixth Brother".
"الأخ السادس".
I'm sorry for being rude yesterday.
أنا آسف لكوني وقح أمس.
I was planning to visit Your Highness to send my apology.
كنت أخطط لزيارة سموك لإرسال اعتذاري.
Little did I know...
لم أكن أعلم ...
Little did I know
لم أكن أعرف سوى القليل
Your Highness would ask me out instead.
صاحب السمو يطلب مني الخروج بدلا من ذلك.
There's no need to be shy around me.
لا داعي للخجل من حولي.
It felt like we hit it off right away.
شعرت أننا ضربناها على الفور.
(I want you to be more proactive.)
(أريدك أن تكون أكثر استباقية.)
Why can't you do me proud?
لماذا لا تفخر بي؟
It seems like
انها تبدو مثل
I have only myself to count on.
لدي نفسي فقط لأعتمد عليه.
What a foolish woman.
يا لها من امرأة حمقاء.
She has made things so much easier for me.
لقد جعلت الأمور أسهل بالنسبة لي.
Miss Liu.
ملكة جمال ليو.
Let me show you the garden.
دعني أريك الحديقة.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
I have investigated it
لقد حققت في ذلك
and found the spy
ووجدوا الجاسوس
Beiqing planted in the Capital
زرعت Beiqing في العاصمة
What about "Yuan Ju Qing"?
ماذا عن "يوان جو تشينغ"؟
I still have no clue about it.
ما زلت ليس لدي أدنى فكرة عن ذلك.
Then, we shall keep waiting
بعد ذلك ، سنواصل الانتظار
and see what Miss Liu
ونرى ما الآنسة ليو
has in store for us.
يوجد في المتجر لنا.
(This is a very suitable place.)
(هذا مكان مناسب جدًا.)
I only need to find the right spot,
أنا فقط بحاجة للعثور على المكان الصحيح ،
and pretend that the stupid woman pushes me into the pond.
وتتظاهر بأن المرأة الغبية دفعتني إلى البركة.
It's a very serene garden.
إنها حديقة هادئة للغاية.
There are goldfish in the pond too.
هناك سمكة ذهبية في البركة أيضًا.
I'm jealous that you get to enjoy your time
أشعر بالغيرة لأنك ستستمتع بوقتك
as a couple here.
كزوجين هنا.
If Miss Liu likes this place,
إذا أعجبت الآنسة ليو بهذا المكان ،
you should visit us
يجب عليك زيارتنا
more often.
في كثير من الأحيان.
(What is she waiting for?)
(ما هو أنها تنتظر؟)
Forget it.
انسى ذلك.
Let me do it myself.
اسمحوا لي أن أفعل ذلك بنفسي.
Miss Liu.
ملكة جمال ليو.
Look.
نظرة.
What is that?
ما هذا؟
Here you go.
ها أنت ذا.
Miss Liu.
ملكة جمال ليو.
Although the fish is cute,
على الرغم من أن السمكة لطيفة ،
you shouldn't have entered the water.
ما كان يجب أن تدخل الماء.
What have I done?
ماذا فعلت؟
Why did Your Highness push me into the pond?
لماذا دفعتني سموك إلى البركة؟
Did I push you?
هل دفعتك؟
I...
أنا...
I guess
اعتقد
I must have accidentally
يجب أن يكون عن طريق الخطأ
bumped into your slim body.
اصطدمت بجسمك النحيف.
I'm so sorry.
أنا آسف جدا.
Let me help you up.
دعني اساعدك
Be careful not to catch a cold.
احرص على عدم الإصابة بنزلة برد.
Hmm...
همم...
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
Hurry up and help Miss Liu up.
أسرع وساعد الآنسة ليو.
Bring her to the room and check her pulse.
أحضرها إلى الغرفة وافحص نبضها.
Hurry up.
عجلوا.
She's going to catch a cold.
سوف تصاب بنزلة برد.
I'll cook you soup.
سوف أطبخ لك الحساء.
I'll be right back.
سأعود حالا.
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
Xiu'er, let's go.
Xiu'er ، دعنا نذهب.
Sure, Young Lady.
بالتأكيد ، سيدة شابة.